# **ADIL TAHIRI**

Software Engineer

## **SUMMARY**

As an accomplished software engineer with a track record of delivering successful web applications. with two years of experience. and successfully do front and back-end web applications. I am enthusiastic about joining a dynamic team to further harness my dedication and skills, and I believe there is so much more I can achieve with dedication and skill

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Software Engineer at 100devs**

January 2022 — Present

- Collaborated with a team of developers to build modern and responsive web applications using best practices
- Built semantically structured full stack web applications for our client and helping each other to achieve our client expectation.

### Freelance in front-end

December 2019 — Present

I build a web application for my client to do more stuff to get an experience lik contribute with an open-source and practice my knowledge to challenge myse and do problem-solving

## Amina salon (Full stack Web App):

This website builds to make anyone can reach and contact the shop owner ar reserve without going to a salon shop and you can check the price and type o style you want.

### special tour (Full stack Web App):

**special tour** is a website that shows you the meaning of adventure and explores the word and gives you some excitement to go see it by yourself

Sami Food delivery & restaurant (Full Stack Web App)

**Sami Food** is a small restaurant and food delivery the meaning of this website is to take a look at the food they offer and where the location is and to reserve a table or order the food from home built with react tailwind firebase and more.

# Other Projects:

**Process bucket:** is full stack app build with JavaScript, NodeJS, mongo dB, CSS, OAuth, and more. I developed a personal finance management website that allows users to track their expenses and view spending patterns through customizable breakdowns on a daily, weekly, monthly, or yearly basis. The dashboard offers clear and visually engaging charts and graphs while implementing robust authentication protocols to protect sensitive user data. Overall, my work on this website demonstrates my skills in full-stack web development, data processing, and UI/UX design.

### CONTACT

#### +212-676538776

Rajaadil19952012@gmail.com

Website

**GitHub** 

LinkedIn

@aadilth

## **SKILLS**

HTML

**CSS** 

**JavaScript** 

React

Node

MongoDB

test

Web Accessibility

API

**TypeScript** 

**Express** 

## **EDUCATION**

## Université Cadi Ayyad

2014 - 2018

Major:

# Languages

Arabic

**English** 

French